It suits you.
似合いますよ
It kind of suits you.
ちょっと似合うね
That's what he looked like until recently.
最近までそんな顔してたってことやねん
amazing?
すごい?
It kind of suits you.
ちょっと似合うね
That's what he looked like until recently.
最近までそんな顔してたってことやねん
amazing?
すごい?
It kind of suits you.
ちょっと似合いますよ
ちょっと似合うね
That's what he looked like until recently.
最近までそんな顔してたってことやねん
Thank you for coming again today.
今日もまた来てくれてありがとうね
What do you think?
どうですか?
Have you gotten used to it?
だいぶ慣れましたか?
a little bit.
ちょっと
Just a little bit?
ちょっとだけ?
It's a nice room.
いい部屋やしね
Yeah, quite a bit.
うん、なかなか
I like it here, me.
ここ気に入ったよ、俺
Yes, it's beautiful.
うん、綺麗
I thought I'd shoot everything here.
ここで全部撮影しようと思ったよ
Your body is white.
体白いですね
I've wanted to meet you ever since.
ここからずっと会いたかったよ、俺は
Yes, thank you very much.
うん、ありがとうございます
After seeing the difference in that world.
あの世の差を見てからね
You're shaking a little.
ちょっと震えてるね